So for any reason you were thinking of not voting today, I'm just going to show you some of the things that these politicians be saying, these lawmakers be saying.
To teach about slavery in Florida and that it was evil. But if we can't have an honest discussion and say that some slaves were paid for their work and were able to actually get a portion of payment that slave owners received for their labor, then we're afraid of teaching accurate history.
Or maybe the kid that went to Harvard and said, hey, you know, that philosophy degree is not worth the paper it's written on. And he went to Pennsylvania gunsmithing school and learned a trade. That's the reality. And I don't think we are. I don't think any of us in this room are missing the opportunity of what school costs. And by the way, you can get college for free. Join the army. I have four. I have three of my four children that did just that.
So there are ways that poor, inner city, black, brown, whatever, they can go to school for free. Join the military.
Will you order mass deportations if you win the White House?
Oh, day one, we have no choice. And we'll start with the bad ones. And you know who knows who they are? Local police. Local police have to be given back their authority. And they have to be given back their respect and immunity. We're going to give them immunity.
And they know by the first name, the middle name and the last name. And they will take them out and they will we will get them out.
We talk about personal responsibility as one of the major principles that the Republican Party stands on.
Yes, I can understand kids going hungry, but is that really the problem of the school district? Is that the problem of the state of North Dakota?
It's really the problem of parents being negligent with their kids if their kids are choosing to eat in the first place, which is entirely the problem that could be existing here.
So if you're thinking about not voting or you didn't vote, just know you're contributing to these people getting to stay in office and talk this bullshit.
And they vote on this bullshit too.
Get in the game.